### ATTA BOATENG

Address: SG1 5TL, 128 Derby way, Stevenage

07436328002, Email: boatengatta68@gmail.com

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Hardworking and passionate nurse assistant with progressive experience giving care to patients. Trained in optimum care, safety standards and documentations requirements. Works great with colleagues and outside departments to coordinate safe and successful care. Careful to follow protocols and guidelines to promote ward efficiency and the delivery of operational skills.

## Skills and Qualities:

- > Patient record management
- Basic wound care and dressing
- > Infection control and management
- First aid, health and safety training
- ➤ Ability to stay calm and tactful under pressure.
- > Critical thinking and problem solving
- ➤ Good time management

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Baptists Medical Centre, Registered General Nurse Assistant April 2019 to September 2023

#### Key responsibilities

- Assisting and providing all forms of basic care such as oral hygiene, bathing, grooming, dressing, exercising and feeding.
- Documents patient's complaints, medical history and updates medication list.
- ➤ Carrying out some procedures such as emptying the urinary catheter bag, changing of soiled linens and laying of bed linens when required.

- Providing emotional, psychological and diversional therapy as need arises.
- ➤ Helping patients take prescribe medicine.
- Preparing and serving healthy meals.
- Accompany to all medical appointments and assist with physiotherapy as need rises
- Run errands such as shopping and picking up prescriptions
- > Supporting clients to function more safely and independently.
- Assessing and treating for pain, nausea and other post-operative symptoms.
- Administration of all forms of medication, implement physician order and perform treatment as prescribed by physician.
- Assist in admission and discharge of patients
- Ensuring wound dressings, bandages and pads are kept in place after surgical procedure.
- ➤ Health education to client and family members on activities contributing to health and recovery such as nutrition, adherence to prescribed medication, exercise and lifestyle management.
- Accurate documentation of findings, care plans and other procedure.
- Decontaminating used instrument before sterilizations, feeding patients through NG tube.
- Evaluate patient responses to interventions and modify plans as needed

# Rose Ananse Memorial Hospice care, Palliative Care February 2017 to March 2019

#### Key responsibilities

- Assisting and providing all forms of basic care such as oral hygiene, bathing, grooming, dressing, exercising and feeding.
- ➤ Documents patient's complaints, medical history and updates medication list.
- ➤ Carrying out some procedures such as emptying the urinary catheter bag, changing of soiled linens and laying of bed linens when required.
- General Assistant, Tesco Heart Building, Welwyn Garden City, November 2023 to Date
- Providing emotional, psychological and diversional therapy as need arises.
- > Helping patients take prescribe medicine.

- > Preparing and serving healthy meals.
- Accompany to all medical appointments and assist with physiotherapy as need rises
- Run errands such as shopping and picking up prescriptions
- > Supporting clients to function more safely and independently

# General Assistant, Tesco Heart Building, Welwyn Garden City November 2023 to Date

### Key responsibilities

- > Greeted and assisted customers in a friendly and professional manner
- Managed appointment schedules and ensured customers were attended to promptly
- Conducted temperature checks and ensured compliance with health and safety regulations
- Provided guidance to customers on testing procedures and answered inquiries
- Assisted with sample collection and administrative tasks as needed
- Maintained cleanliness and organization of the testing centre
- > Collaborated with team members to ensure efficient operation of the centre
- Assisting and providing all forms of basic care such as oral hygiene, bathing, grooming, dressing, exercising and feeding.
- Documents patient's complaints, medical history and updates medication list.
- ➤ Carrying out some procedures such as emptying the urinary catheter bag, changing of soiled linens and laying of bed linens when required.
- Providing emotional, psychological and diversional therapy as need arises.
- ➤ Helping patients take prescribe medicine.
- Preparing and serving healthy meals.

# **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATION**

Mampong Nursing and midwifery training college, Nurse Assistant (Clinical)

Mampong - Ashanti, August, 2014 – November, 2016

Nsutaman Senior High School WASSCE April 2008 - June 2012

Ghana Baptist University College-Abuakwa in collaboration with Oxford Brookes University, Palliative care Training certificate 25th November 2019-29th November 2019

# **References**

Dr. Ernest Kweku Amankwah Medical Superintendent Baptist Medical Center, Abuakwa dillingio@yahoo.co.uk.

Zobari Joy Deekae Assistant Manager Tesco Heart Building Zobari.deekae@tesco.com